# **GODWIN FESTUS**

godwinfestus8@gmail.com | 09121804908, 09137788447 | https://www.linkedin.com/in/godwin-festus/ https://raveex12.github.io/FestusGodwinPortfolio.io/

### **SUMMARY**

Organized, dedicated and ambitious budding professional with excellent attention to detail, and thirst for learning and passion for excellence. Impact-driven with more than 1 year working experience in Fintech industry. Possess good communication, and organization skill and the ability to function in a team. Adept in working with technologies in the field of data science and analytics and possess good knowledge of the following:

Skills: Python, SQL, Spreadsheets (MS Excel and Google), Tableau, Power BI

#### **EDUCATION**

Associates of Estate Management and Valuation - Auchi Polytechnic, Auchi Degree - Distinction (CGPA: 3.7/4)

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

**Data Science Micro Degree** – Ustacky.com Google Data Analytics Specialization – Coursera.org **Diploma in Computer Application – Net-links Computer Training Institute**  October 2022 January 2022 September 2013

### **EXPERIENCE**

# September 2020 – Present

# Aggregator | *Opay Digital Services*

- Analyze Mobile Money Agent's performance using key performance indicators
- Onboard New Mobile Money Agents
- Marketing and Sales
- Analyze life dashboard for effective management of Agents
- Dashboard Reporting
- Agent Performance analysis

# June 2016 – August 2019 Mathematics and Statistics Tutor | Noble International Academy

- Preparation of lesson plans,
- Presentation, evaluation, and analysis of students' performance using key performance indicators,
- preparation of report presentation,
- Organization, and management of Academic staff

# September 2019 – December 2021

# Student Tutor | Auchi polytechnic, Auchi

- Developed and taught courses in Environmental sciences such as Valuation, Statistics, Logic, and Algebra
- Increased Statistics passed rate by 10%

### PROJECTS IN DATA SCIENCE

January 2022 Bella bit Analysis August 2022 Performance analysis of Store XYZ

October 2022 Impact the of covid19 pandemic on Nigeria's Economy